(screams)
- Thank you very much.
(crowd excitement)
- Ladies and gentlemen,
we'd like to do the song
that was my very biggest
record last year.
I mean, it was no bigger
than the rest of them.
(audience laughs)
- But sold a few more.
And we'd like to tell you that
to all the people watching
and all you people
that are here tonight,
that we really are thankful
for all the success
that you made us
have and everything.
This is my biggest rack...record
and it goes something like this.
(screams)
♪ You know I can be found ♪
♪ Sittin' home all alone ♪
♪ If you can't come around ♪
♪ At least please telephone ♪
♪ Don't be cruel to
a heart that's true ♪
♪ Well baby if I made you mad ♪
♪ For somethin' I
might have said ♪
♪ Please let's forget my past ♪
♪ The future looks
bright ahead ♪
♪ Don't be cruel to
a heart that's true ♪
♪ I don't want no other love ♪
♪ Baby it's just you
I'm thinkin' of ♪
♪ Mmmmm ♪
(screams)
♪ Hey don't stop
thinkin' about me ♪
♪ Don't make me feel this way ♪
♪ Come on over
here and love me ♪
♪ You know what I
want you to say ♪
♪ Don't be cruel to
a heart that's true ♪
♪ Why should we be apart? ♪
♪ I really love you
baby, cross my heart. ♪
♪ Let's walk up
to the preacher ♪
♪ And let's say 'I do' ♪
♪ Then you'll know
you'll have me ♪
♪ And I know I'll have you too ♪
♪ Don't be cruel to
a heart that's true ♪
♪ I don't want no other love ♪
♪ Baby, it's just
you I'm thinking of ♪
♪ Don't be cruel (oo-oo-oo) ♪
♪ To a heart that's true ♪
- Here we go.
♪ Well, I don't
want no other love ♪
♪ Baby, it's just
you I'm thinking of ♪
(screams)
- Oh, I wish I were young again.
No fooling, that's
wonderful to be that way.
Good.